{
    "id": "e9e2139e4ac04a878da8cbbe6befdf7b",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. we visit Ajanta and Ellora? (Making a suggestion)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab46985e970741dfb5497d68a269b06c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you come with us? (Asking a question)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "66edd6f5c9d946ee89c345aa894b545d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he play for our team? (Asking a question about future possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "052579ab89b941199f60830680488f97"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. they advertise the post? (Asking a question about future possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49864cb3b5b44ebead2bd9d8122ae3f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I get a prize if I stand first in the examination?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e9d57209b5d49868440381f464f048b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Captain said, ‘Players ………………… assemble at the College at 4 P.M.’ (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84885a3df1e74a8ca5100fa38f35d099"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said, ‘The scoundrel ……………….. thrashed.’ (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "shall be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21619fdedd224c00a2780027d8bdd09a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. not be unfair to him. (duty)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "655f31ed8e0048a08fbd9c61d55be425"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………. all work for the common good. (duty or necessity",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b851ae6095d74b4b940ccd30500a41ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. tell the truth. (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b09c98114fb74233aa682658c4f4af29"
        }
    ]
}